<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Sensio Air</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="facebook_app_id" translatable="false">993708130718989</string>  <!-- 1123364724382074 : test -->  <!-- 1122387414479805 : living --> <!-- 993708130718989 : client -->

    <!-- Common Button String-->
    <string name="Tag_Yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="Tag_No">No</string>
    <string name="Tag_Ok">OK</string>
    <string name="Tag_Retry">RETRY</string>
    <string name="Tag_Cancel">Cancelar</string>
    <string name="Tag_Submit">Enviar</string>
    <string name="Tag_SubmitCaps">Enviar</string>

    <string-array name="Gender">
        <item>male</item>
        <item>female</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- GCM Push notification -->
    <string name="gcm_send_message">Token retrieved and sent to server! You can now use gcmsender to
        send downstream messages to this app.</string>
    <string name="registering_message">Generating InstanceID token...</string>
    <string name="token_error_message">An error occurred while either fetching the InstanceID token,
        sending the fetched token to the server or subscribing to the PubSub topic. Please try
        running the sample again.</string>

    <!-- Font Name -->
    <string name="font_name_opensans">OpenSans</string>
    <string name="font_name_path_opensans">font/OpenSans-SemiboldItalic.ttf</string>

    <!-- Strings related to Terms and Condition -->
    <string name="title_terms">TERMS &amp; CONDITIONS</string>
    <string name="content_terms">Please read the followings terms before using your iOS device,. By using your iOS device, you are agreeeing to be bound by the OS terms and conditions.</string>
    <string name="button_accept">ACCEPT &amp; CONTINUE</string>
    <string name="button_continue">CONTINUE</string>

    <!-- Strings related to login -->
    <string name="title_activity_login">Sign in</string>
    <string name="prompt_username">Username</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password</string>
    <string name="action_new_account"><u>Create New Account</u></string>
    <string name="action_forgot_password"><u>Forgot Password</u></string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">GET STARTED!</string>
    <string name="description_login">Tells you what\'s in the \nair you breathe</string>
    <string name="description_otherlogin">Or Login with</string>
    <string name="description_license">I accept the terms and conditions</string>

    <string name="error_invalid_password">This password is too short</string>
    <string name="error_incorrect_password">This password is incorrect</string>
    <string name="error_field_required">This field is required</string>
    <string name="password_hint">Password</string>
    <string name="email_hint">Email</string>

    <!-- Strings related to Create Account -->
    <string name="title_activity_signup">Create Account</string>
    <string name="title_create_account">CREATE ACCOUNT</string>
    <string name="hint_firstname">First name</string>
    <string name="hint_lastname">Last name</string>
    <string name="hint_phonenum">Phone Number</string>
    <string name="hint_countrycode">Code</string>
    <string name="hint_birthday">Date of birth</string>
    <string name="hint_gender">Gender</string>
    <string name="chb_male">Male</string>
    <string name="chb_female">Female</string>
    <string name="chb_geolocation">Allow geolocation</string>
    <string name="chb_subscribe">Subscribe to newsletter</string>
    <string name="btn_register">REGISTER</string>
    <string name="otherregister">Or Register with</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login_acitivity">Sign in</string>
    <string name="not_parsing">Response Error</string>
    <string name="msg_not_city">Outdoor Data for your city is not yet available</string>

    <!-- Strings related to About Health -->
    <string name="title_activity_health">Your Health</string>
    <string name="title_health">TELL US MORE ABOUT \nYOUR HEALTH</string>
    <string name="chb_conscious">I\'m just health conscious.</string>
    <string name="chb_allergies">I have allergies, asthma:</string>
    <string name="chb_eyes">Eyes</string>
    <string name="chb_nose">Nose</string>
    <string name="chb_lungs">Lungs</string>
    <string name="hint_specify">Please specify</string>
    <string name="chb_respiratory">I have another respiratory distress</string>
    <string name="chb_pet">I have a pet at home</string>
    <string name="btn_save_continue">SAVE &amp; CONTINUE</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home">HomeActivity</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>

    <!-- Strings related to Home -->
    <string name="btn_home">Home</string>
    <string name="btn_statistics">Statistics</string>
    <string name="btn_preorder">Pre-order</string>
    <string name="btn_sensio">Sensio</string>
    <string name="btn_profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="btn_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_sympton">SymptonActivity</string>
    <string name="item_menu_loading">Loading...</string>

    <!-- Strings related to Select Symptom -->
    <string name="title_symptom">SELECT SYMPTOM</string>
    <string name="description_symptom">Press to modify the\nintensity of your symptom</string>
    <string name="btnSubmit">SUBMIT</string>

    <!-- Strings related to Settings -->
    <string name="title_settings">SETTINGS</string>
    <string name="description_settings">Set the sensitivity level\nfor your notifications:</string>
    <string name="btn_senddata">Send your data via Email</string>
    <string name="btn_savesettings">Save settings</string>
    <!--<string name=""></string>-->

    <!-- Strings of Alert -->
    <string name="title_message">Message</string>
    <string name="title_alert">Alert</string>
    <string name="title_notice">Notice</string>
    <string name="check_internet">Please check your internet settings!!!</string>
    <string name="try_again">Error, Please try again later</string>
    <string name="register_fail">Registration fail. Please Try Again</string>
    <string name="email_used">This Email has being used by another account</string>
    <string name="email_notprovided">Email Not Provided</string>
    <string name="incorrect_hash">Incorrect Hash</string>
    <string name="email_unable">Unable to Send Email</string>
    <string name="register_success">Register Success</string>
    <string name="user_suspended">Your account suspended. Please contact our team.</string>
    <string name="reset_password">You need to reset your password.</string>
    <string name="userid_not">UserID Not Provided</string>
    <string name="device_not">This ID of device is not provided.</string>
    <string name="http_error">HTTP Agent Provided or Not HTTPS</string>
    <string name="incorrect_pass">Incorrect Username or Password</string>
    <string name="not_found">Device not found</string>
    <string name="no_exist">This account does not exist.</string>
    <string name="not_save_setting">Your settings are not saved. Please try again after a moment.</string>
    <string name="no_saved_info">No Saved Info.</string>
    <string name="nothing_found">You saved info didn\'t find.</string>
    <string name="not_sendable">Unable to Send Email</string>
    <string name="email_noexist">Email Does not exist</string>
    <string name="input_email">Please input your correct Email</string>
    <string name="savingsetting_success">Saved your settings successfully.</string>
    <string name="senduserinfo_success">Your info was sent successfully.</string>
    <string name="forgotpass_msg_format">Forgot your password?\nEmail: %s</string>
    <string name="forgot_success">A new password has been sent to your email.</string>
    <string name="select_symptom">You have to select at least 1 symptom.</string>
    <string name="feedback_success">Thank You for Your Feedback.</string>
    <string name="msg_facebook_error">Facebook login Error</string>
    <string name="not_saved_info">Saving your information failed.</string>

    <!--<string name="try">Please</string>-->

    <!-- Strings related to Sensio Page-->
    <string name="str_scanning">Scanning...</string>
    <string name="str_scann_qrcode">SCAN THE QR CODE ON\nTHE BACK OF THE DEVICE</string>
    <string name="str_nodevice">Don\'t have the device?</string>
    <string name="btn_sensio_now"><u>Pre-order it now!</u></string>

    <!-- Strings related to Profile -->
    <string name="title_profile">PROFILE</string>
    <string name="profile_item1">I\'m just health conscious</string>
    <string name="profile_item2">I have nose allergies</string>
    <string name="profile_item3">I don\'t respiratory distress</string>
    <string name="profile_item4">I have a pet at home</string>
    <string name="btn_editinfo">Edit info</string>
    <string name="btn_feedback">Give us your feedback</string>
    <string name="btn_logout">Log out</string>
    <string name="label_finddoctor">FINDE A DOCTOR\nNEAR YOU</string>
    <string name="btn_chemist">Register as a Chemist or Physician</string>

    <string name="title_feedback">GIVE US YOUR\nFEEDBACK</string>


    <!-- Strings related to sub-statistics page-->
    <string name="sub_title_particular">Particular Matter</string>
    <string name="content_particular">32 ppm/2.5</string>
    <string name="sub_title_humidity">Humidity</string>
    <string name="content_humidity">78%</string>
    <string name="sub_title_pollen">Pollen Count</string>
    <string name="content_pollen">28 ppm/L</string>
    <string name="sub_title_harmful">Harmful gasses</string>
    <string name="content_harmful">32 p/L</string>
    <string name="sub_title_temperature">Temperature</string>
    <string name="content_temperature">32 o C</string>
    <string name="sub_title_sunlight">Sunlight</string>
    <string name="content_sunlight">950 LX</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_close">CloseActivity</string>

    <!-- Home Activity -->
    <string name="titleMessage">Sensio Air</string>
    
    <!-- Tutorial String -->
    <string name="tutorial_home_index">Welcome!\nSensio tells you about the environment in your city.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_home_press">Here you can log your allergies and respiratory symptoms.(Tap the red button)</string>
    <string name="tutorial_home_press_2">With our smart algorithms and board of doctors, Sensio gives you daily advices on how to deal with the outdoor pollution and improve the air at home.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_statisticss">Sensio helps you understand your symptoms by linking them to your environment.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_sensio_scanning">By scanning the QR Code on the back of the device, Sensio Air monitors the health of your home and tells you all about pollution, allergens, dust, mold and so much more.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_sensio">Want to know more about the Air at home? You can order Sensio Air Home Edition.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_sympotom">Here you can tap repetitevely to record your symtpom. (Try it!).</string>

    <string name="test_string">This is TEST String.<u>Pre-order</u> it <b>now</b>!</string>
    <string name="terms_condition">
<![CDATA[
<p><strong>Agreement  between user and Wlab.io</strong><br/>
  Welcome  to wlab.io. The wlab.io app (or the &quot;Site&quot;) is comprised of various  pages operated by WLab LTD (&quot;Wlab&quot;). Wlab.io is offered to you  conditioned on your acceptance without modification of the terms, conditions,  and notices contained herein (the &quot;Terms&quot;). Your use of wlab.io  constitutes your agreement to all such Terms. Please read these terms  carefully, and keep a copy of them for your reference.</p>
<p>Wlab.io  is an analytics company,&nbsp;White Lab LTD provides data and advice as a  general information and cannot replace the diagnostic of a health professional.  When you use our device or application please know that you use them at your  own risk and they cannot in anyway replace professional advice.</p>
<p><strong>Privacy</strong><br/>
  Your  use of wlab.io is subject to Wlab\'s Privacy Policy. Please review our Privacy  Policy, which also governs the app and informs users of our data collection  practices.</p>
<p><strong>Electronic  Communications</strong><br/>
  Visiting  wlab.io or sending emails to Wlab constitutes electronic communications. You  consent to receive electronic communications and you agree that all agreements,  notices, disclosures and other communications that we provide to you  electronically, via email and on the Site, satisfy any legal requirement that  such communications be in writing.</p>
<p><strong>Your  account</strong><br/>
  If  you use this site, you are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of  your account and password and for restricting access to your computer, and you  agree to accept responsibility for all activities that occur under your account  or password. You may not assign or otherwise transfer your account to any other  person or entity. You acknowledge that Wlab is not responsible for third party  access to your account that results from theft or misappropriation of your  account. Wlab and its associates reserve the right to refuse or cancel service,  terminate accounts, or remove or edit content in our sole discretion.</p>
<p>In  the case of minors or children you may log the outbreaks of your child at your  own risk, please remember that our products do not replace the advice of a  Doctor or health professional.&nbsp;</p>
<p>If  you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for  permission to use this website. If you are a parent and you have questions  regarding our data collection practices, please contact us using the  information provided at the end of this Agreement. If you are under 18, you may  use wlab.io only with permission of a parent or guardian.</p>
<p><strong>Cancellation/Refund  Policy</strong><br/>
  You  may cancel your subscription to our services at any time by removing the  application from your phone, should you want to purchase Sensio Air the device,  please know that you will be using it under your own responsability.</p>
<p><strong>Links  to third party sites/Third party services</strong><br/>
  wlab.io  may contain links to other websites (&quot;Linked Sites&quot;). The Linked  Sites are not under the control of Wlab and Wlab is not responsible for the  contents of any Linked Site, including without limitation any link contained in  a Linked Site, or any changes or updates to a Linked Site. Wlab is providing  these links to you only as a convenience, and the inclusion of any link does  not imply endorsement by Wlab of the site or any association with its  operators.</p>
<p>Certain  services made available via wlab.io are delivered by third party sites and  organizations. By using any product, service or functionality originating from  the wlab.io domain, you hereby acknowledge and consent that Wlab may share such  information and data with any third party with whom Wlab has a contractual  relationship to provide the requested product, service or functionality on  behalf of wlab.io users and customers.</p>
<p><strong>No unlawful or prohibited use/Intellectual Property </strong><br/>
  You  are granted a non-exclusive, non-transferable, revocable license to access and  use wlab.io strictly in accordance with these terms of use. As a condition of  your use of the Site, you warrant to Wlab that you will not use the Site for  any purpose that is unlawful or prohibited by these Terms. You may not use the  Site in any manner which could damage, disable, overburden, or impair the Site  or interfere with any other party\'s use and enjoyment of the Site. You may not  obtain or attempt to obtain any materials or information through any means not  intentionally made available or provided for through the Site.</p>
<p>All  content included as part of the Service, such as text, graphics, logos, images,  as well as the compilation thereof, and any software used on the Site, is the  property of Wlab or its suppliers and protected by copyright and other laws  that protect intellectual property and proprietary rights. You agree to observe  and abide by all copyright and other proprietary notices, legends or other  restrictions contained in any such content and will not make any changes  thereto.</p>
<p>You  will not modify, publish, transmit, reverse engineer, participate in the  transfer or sale, create derivative works, or in any way exploit any of the  content, in whole or in part, found on the Site. Wlab content is not for  resale. Your use of the Site does not entitle you to make any unauthorized use  of any protected content, and in particular you will not delete or alter any  proprietary rights or attribution notices in any content. You will use  protected content solely for your personal use, and will make no other use of  the content without the express written permission of Wlab and the copyright  owner. You agree that you do not acquire any ownership rights in any protected  content. We do not grant you any licenses, express or implied, to the  intellectual property of Wlab or our licensors except as expressly authorized  by these Terms.</p>
<p><strong>Use  of communication services</strong><br/>
  The  App may contain bulletin board services, chat areas, news groups, forums,  communities, personal web pages, calendars, and/or other message or  communication facilities designed to enable you to communicate with the public  at large or with a group (collectively, &quot;Communication Services&quot;),  you agree to use the Communication Services only to post, send and receive  messages and material that are proper and related to the particular  Communication Service.</p>
<p>By  way of example, and not as a limitation, you agree that when using a  Communication Service, you will not: defame, abuse, harass, stalk, threaten or  otherwise violate the legal rights (such as rights of privacy and publicity) of  others; publish, post, upload, distribute or disseminate any inappropriate,  profane, defamatory, infringing, obscene, indecent or unlawful topic, name,  material or information; upload files that contain software or other material  protected by intellectual property laws (or by rights of privacy of publicity)  unless you own or control the rights thereto or have received all necessary  consents; upload files that contain viruses, corrupted files, or any other  similar software or programs that may damage the operation of another\'s  computer; advertise or offer to sell or buy any goods or services for any  business purpose, unless such Communication Service specifically allows such  messages; conduct or forward surveys, contests, pyramid schemes or chain  letters; download any file posted by another user of a Communication Service  that you know, or reasonably should know, cannot be legally distributed in such  manner; falsify or delete any author attributions, legal or other proper  notices or proprietary designations or labels of the origin or source of  software or other material contained in a file that is uploaded, restrict or  inhibit any other user from using and enjoying the Communication Services;  violate any code of conduct or other guidelines which may be applicable for any  particular Communication Service; harvest or otherwise collect information  about others, including e-mail addresses, without their consent; violate any  applicable laws or regulations.</p>
<p>Wlab  has no obligation to monitor the Communication Services. However, Wlab reserves  the right to review materials posted to a Communication Service and to remove  any materials in its sole discretion. Wlab reserves the right to terminate your  access to any or all of the Communication Services at any time without notice  for any reason whatsoever.</p>
<p>Wlab  reserves the right at all times to disclose any information as necessary to  satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request,  or to edit, refuse to post or to remove any information or materials, in whole  or in part, in Wlab\'s sole discretion.</p>
<p>Always  use caution when giving out any personally identifying information about  yourself or your children in any Communication Service. Wlab does not control  or endorse the content, messages or information found in any Communication  Service and, therefore, Wlab specifically disclaims any liability with regard  to the Communication Services and any actions resulting from your participation  in any Communication Service. Managers and hosts are not authorized Wlab  spokespersons, and their views do not necessarily reflect those of Wlab.</p>
<p>Materials  uploaded to a Communication Service may be subject to posted limitations on  usage, reproduction and/or dissemination. You are responsible for adhering to  such limitations if you upload the materials.</p>
<p><strong>Materials  provided to wlab.io or posted on any Wlab web page</strong><br/>
  Wlab  does not claim ownership of the materials you provide to wlab.io (including  feedback and suggestions) or post, upload, input or submit to any Wlab Site or  our associated services (collectively &quot;Submissions&quot;). However, by  posting, uploading, inputting, providing or submitting your Submission you are  granting Wlab, our affiliated companies and necessary sublicensees permission  to use your Submission in connection with the operation of their Internet  businesses including, without limitation, the rights to: copy, distribute,  transmit, publicly display, publicly perform, reproduce, edit, translate and  reformat your Submission; and to publish your name in connection with your  Submission.</p>
<p>No  compensation will be paid with respect to the use of your Submission, as  provided herein. Wlab is under no obligation to post or use any Submission you  may provide and may remove any Submission at any time in Wlab\'s sole  discretion.</p>
<p>By  posting, uploading, inputting, providing or submitting your Submission you  warrant and represent that you own or otherwise control all of the rights to  your Submission as described in this section including, without limitation, all  the rights necessary for you to provide, post, upload, input or submit the  Submissions.</p>
<p><strong>Third  Party Accounts</strong><br/>
  You  will be able to connect your Wlab account to third party accounts. By  connecting your Wlab account to your third party account, you acknowledge and  agree that you are consenting to the continuous release of information about  you to others (in accordance with your privacy settings on those third party  sites). If you do not want information about you to be shared in this manner,  do not use this feature.</p>
<p><strong>International  Users</strong><br/>
  The  Service is controlled, operated and administered by Wlab from our offices  within the USA. If you access the Service from a location outside the USA, you  are responsible for compliance with all local laws. You agree that you will not  use the Wlab Content accessed through wlab.io in any country or in any manner  prohibited by any applicable laws, restrictions or regulations.</p>
<p><strong>Indemnification</strong><br/>
  You  agree to indemnify, defend and hold harmless Wlab, its officers, directors,  employees, agents and third parties, for any losses, costs, liabilities and  expenses (including reasonable attorney\'s fees) relating to or arising out of  your use of or inability to use the Site or services, any user postings made by  you, your violation of any terms of this Agreement or your violation of any  rights of a third party, or your violation of any applicable laws, rules or  regulations. Wlab reserves the right, at its own cost, to assume the exclusive  defense and control of any matter otherwise subject to indemnification by you,  in which event you will fully cooperate with Wlab in asserting any available  defenses.</p>
<p><strong>Arbitration</strong><br/>
  In  the event the parties are not able to resolve any dispute between them arising  out of or concerning these Terms and Conditions, or any provisions hereof,  whether in contract, tort, or otherwise at law or in equity for damages or any  other relief, then such dispute shall be resolved only by final and binding  arbitration pursuant to the Federal Arbitration Act, conducted by a single  neutral arbitrator and administered by the American Arbitration Association, or  a similar arbitration service selected by the parties, in a location mutually  agreed upon by the parties. The arbitrators award shall be final, and judgment  may be entered upon it in any court having jurisdiction. In the event that any legal  or equitable action, proceeding or arbitration arises out of or concerns these  Terms and Conditions, the prevailing party shall be entitled to recover its  costs and reasonable attorney\'s fees. The parties agree to arbitrate all  disputes and claims in regards to these Terms and Conditions or any disputes  arising as a result of these Terms and Conditions, whether directly or  indirectly, including Tort claims that are a result of these Terms and  Conditions. The parties agree that the Federal Arbitration Act governs the  interpretation and enforcement of this provision. The entire dispute, including  the scope and enforceability of this arbitration provision shall be determined  by the Arbitrator. This arbitration provision shall survive the termination of  these Terms and Conditions.</p>
<p><strong>Class  Action Waiver</strong><br/>
  Any  arbitration under these Terms and Conditions will take place on an individual  basis; class arbitrations and class/representative/collective actions are not  permitted. THE PARTIES AGREE THAT A PARTY MAY BRING CLAIMS AGAINST THE OTHER  ONLY IN EACH\'S INDIVIDUAL CAPACITY, AND NOT AS A PLAINTIFF OR CLASS MEMBER IN  ANY PUTATIVE CLASS, COLLECTIVE AND/ OR REPRESENTATIVE PROCEEDING, SUCH AS IN  THE FORM OF A PRIVATE ATTORNEY GENERAL ACTION AGAINST THE OTHER. Further, unless  both you and Employer agree otherwise, the arbitrator may not consolidate more  than one person\'s claims, and may not otherwise preside over any form of a  representative or class proceeding.</p>
<p><strong>Liability  disclaimer</strong><br/>
  THE  INFORMATION, SOFTWARE, PRODUCTS, AND SERVICES INCLUDED IN OR AVAILABLE THROUGH  THE SITE MAY INCLUDE INACCURACIES OR TYPOGRAPHICAL ERRORS. CHANGES ARE  PERIODICALLY ADDED TO THE INFORMATION HEREIN. WLAB LTD AND/OR ITS SUPPLIERS MAY  MAKE IMPROVEMENTS AND/OR CHANGES IN THE SITE AT ANY TIME.</p>
<p>WLAB  LTD AND/OR ITS SUPPLIERS MAKE NO REPRESENTATIONS ABOUT THE SUITABILITY,  RELIABILITY, AVAILABILITY, TIMELINESS, AND ACCURACY OF THE INFORMATION,  SOFTWARE, PRODUCTS, SERVICES AND RELATED GRAPHICS CONTAINED ON THE SITE FOR ANY  PURPOSE. TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, ALL SUCH  INFORMATION, SOFTWARE, PRODUCTS, SERVICES AND RELATED GRAPHICS ARE PROVIDED  &quot;AS IS&quot; WITHOUT WARRANTY OR CONDITION OF ANY KIND. WLAB LTD AND/OR  ITS SUPPLIERS HEREBY DISCLAIM ALL WARRANTIES AND CONDITIONS WITH REGARD TO THIS  INFORMATION, SOFTWARE, PRODUCTS, SERVICES AND RELATED GRAPHICS, INCLUDING ALL  IMPLIED WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR  PURPOSE, TITLE AND NON-INFRINGEMENT.</p>
<p>TO  THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, IN NO EVENT SHALL WLAB LTD  AND/OR ITS SUPPLIERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, PUNITIVE, INCIDENTAL,  SPECIAL, CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES OR ANY DAMAGES WHATSOEVER INCLUDING, WITHOUT  LIMITATION, DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF USE, DATA OR PROFITS, ARISING OUT OF OR IN ANY  WAY CONNECTED WITH THE USE OR PERFORMANCE OF THE SITE, WITH THE DELAY OR  INABILITY TO USE THE SITE OR RELATED SERVICES, THE PROVISION OF OR FAILURE TO  PROVIDE SERVICES, OR FOR ANY INFORMATION, SOFTWARE, PRODUCTS, SERVICES AND  RELATED GRAPHICS OBTAINED THROUGH THE SITE, OR OTHERWISE ARISING OUT OF THE USE  OF THE SITE, WHETHER BASED ON CONTRACT, TORT, NEGLIGENCE, STRICT LIABILITY OR  OTHERWISE, EVEN IF WLAB LTD OR ANY OF ITS SUPPLIERS HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE  POSSIBILITY OF DAMAGES. BECAUSE SOME STATES/JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE  EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF LIABILITY FOR CONSEQUENTIAL OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES,  THE ABOVE LIMITATION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. IF YOU ARE DISSATISFIED WITH ANY  PORTION OF THE SITE, OR WITH ANY OF THESE TERMS OF USE, YOUR SOLE AND EXCLUSIVE  REMEDY IS TO DISCONTINUE USING THE SITE.</p>
<p><strong>Termination/access  restriction </strong><br/>
  Wlab  reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to terminate your access to the  Site and the related services or any portion thereof at any time, without  notice. To the maximum extent permitted by law, this agreement is governed by  the laws of the State of _________________ and you hereby consent to the  exclusive jurisdiction and venue of courts in _________________ in all disputes  arising out of or relating to the use of the Site. Use of the Site is  unauthorized in any jurisdiction that does not give effect to all provisions of  these Terms, including, without limitation, this section.</p>
<p>You  agree that no joint venture, partnership, employment, or agency relationship  exists between you and Wlab as a result of this agreement or use of the Site.  Wlab\'s performance of this agreement is subject to existing laws and legal  process, and nothing contained in this agreement is in derogation of Wlab\'s  right to comply with governmental, court and law enforcement requests or  requirements relating to your use of the Site or information provided to or  gathered by Wlab with respect to such use. If any part of this agreement is  determined to be invalid or unenforceable pursuant to applicable law including,  but not limited to, the warranty disclaimers and liability limitations set  forth above, then the invalid or unenforceable provision will be deemed  superseded by a valid, enforceable provision that most closely matches the  intent of the original provision and the remainder of the agreement shall  continue in effect.</p>
<p>Unless  otherwise specified herein, this agreement constitutes the entire agreement  between the user and Wlab with respect to the Site and it supersedes all prior  or contemporaneous communications and proposals, whether electronic, oral or  written, between the user and Wlab with respect to the Site. A printed version  of this agreement and of any notice given in electronic form shall be  admissible in judicial or administrative proceedings based upon or relating to  this agreement to the same extent and subject to the same conditions as other  business documents and records originally generated and maintained in printed  form. It is the express wish to the parties that this agreement and all related  documents be written in English.</p>
<p><strong>Changes  to Terms</strong><br/>
  Wlab  reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to change the Terms under which  wlab.io is offered. The most current version of the Terms will supersede all  previous versions. Wlab encourages you to periodically review the Terms to stay  informed of our updates.</p>
<p><strong>Contact  Us</strong><br/>
  Wlab  welcomes your questions or comments regarding the Terms:</p>
<p>WLab  LTD<br/>
  103c  Camley street<br/>
  London,  United Kingdom, N1C 4PF</p>
<p>Email  Address:<br/>
  <a href="mailto:sensio@wsurw.com">sensio@wsurw.com</a></p>
<p>Effective  as of March 29, 2016</p>
]]>
    </string>
</resources>
